[SINGING ALONG TO RADIO]
Goin' out tonight
I'm feelin' all right
Gonna let it all hang out
Wanna make some noise
Really raise my voice
Yeah, I wanna scream and shout
Unh! No--
(Penny:)Morning, Sheldon. Come dance with me.
(Sheldon:)No.
(Penny:)Why not?
(Sheldon:)Penny, while I subscribe
to the Many-Worlds theory...
...which posits the existence of infinite
Sheldons in an infinite number...
(Sheldon:)...of universes, I assure you
that none of them am I dancing.
(Penny:)Are you fun in any of them?
(Sheldon:)The math would suggest that in a few,
I'm a clown made of candy.
(Sheldon:)But I don't dance.
(Penny:)-All right, want some French toast?
-It's oatmeal day.
(Penny:)Tell you what, next French toast day,
I will make you oatmeal.